Guide to the Walter Tobriner papers, 1949-1968 MS2014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Walter Tobriner papers
1949-1968
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Tobriner, Walter
MS2014
9.25 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, greeting cards, index cards, newspaper clippings, speeches, statements, publications, and various types of memorabilia. The bulk of the collection consists of the six scrapbooks constructed by Tobriner between 1961 and 1968. These scrapbooks were taken apart and preservation photocopied, then placed in their original order, along with the different kinds of memorabilia. The materials in this collection range in date from 1949 to 1968, with the bulk of the material dating between 1961 and 1968. Most of these records represent the period in which Tobriner served on the Board of Education and Board of Commissioners.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated to the Gelman Library in 1969 by Mrs. Walter Tobriner.
Historical or Biographical Note
Walter Nathan Tobriner (1902-1979) was born to Leon and Blanch Tobriner on July 2, in Washington D.C. After attending the Sidwell Friends School up through the eleventh grade, he went on to study at Princeton University. He graduated with a Bachelor of Arts degree from Princeton University in 1923, and later received his law degree from Harvard University in 1926. In 1927 Tobriner was admitted to the bar and began to practice law in the Washington, D.C. area. From 1927 to 1950, he was also a professor of law at the National University School for Law. On July 20, 1933, he was married to Marienne Smith. His only lapse in teaching was from 1943-46, when he served as a Lt. Colonel in the Army Air Force. Tobriner served as the president of the board of the Garfield Memorial Hospital from 1952 to 1955. In 1954, he also was president of the board of the Lisner Home for Women. Tobriner acquired the position as director of the Blue Cross Plan in 1953 and maintained this position until 1961. He also headed the board of the Washington Hospital Center from 1959 to 1961.
Tobriner's hard work earned him a spot on the Washington Board of Education from 1952-1961. He served as president of the board from 1957 to 1961, during which time was responsible for carrying out the Supreme Court decision of 1954 which required the desegregation of public schools. He also served as a delegate to the Democratic National Convention in the years 1956, 1960, and 1964. Then in 1961 President Kennedy appointed him to the Board of Commissioners for Washington D.C. where he served from 1961 to 1967. In fact, he served as the last president of the Board of Commissioners in 1967 when the government of Washington, D.C. underwent reorganization. During this same time, as Chairman of the National Housing Authority, Tobriner brought about fair housing and employment ordinances, aimed at ending racial discrimination. He was a trustee of the National Cultural Center from 1964-67. From 1966 to 1967 he was also the chairman of the Washington Metro Area Transit Authority, when the first contracts for the new subway system contracts were awarded. In the period from 1967 to 1969, Tobriner was appointed as the United States Ambassador to Jamaica. In addition, the U.S. Department of State needed his help as a consultant in 1969. Tobriner had also been a member of the Committee of 100 on the Federal City from 1974 up until his death in 1979.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, greeting cards, index cards, newspaper clippings, speeches, statements, publications, and various types of memorabilia. The bulk of the collection consists of the six scrapbooks constructed by Tobriner between 1961 and 1968. These scrapbooks were taken apart and preservation photocopied, then placed in their original order, along with the different kinds of memorabilia. The materials in this collection range in date from 1949 to 1968, with the bulk of the material dating between 1961 and 1968. Most of these records represent the period in which Tobriner served on the Board of Education and Board of Commissioners.
The predominant subject material within this collection relates to Desegregation/Integration in public schools, especially in the context of Washington D.C. Area public school systems. Many of the publications, news clippings, and statements reflect Tobriner's strive for educational equality. The scrapbooks provide a chronological record of Tobriner's political and social activities in the years they cover. Much of the this material deals with topics such as civil rights, school reforms, transportation issues in the Washington Metropolitan Region, and city beautification. In addition, limited material exists from the time that Tobriner served as the United States Ambassador to Jamaica. There is also a good selection of presidential memorabilia, especially from John F. Kennedy's term in office, as well as numerous other types of memorabilia which comes from various civic and private functions.
Collection Organization
The collection is organized into five series: Correspondence, Newspaper clippings, Speeches/statements/remarks, Publications, and Scrapbooks.
Washington (D.C.); Housing; Presidents; Discrimination; Civil rights; Transportation; Segregation; Education; Scrapbooks; Tobriner, Walter; Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority
- Correspondence, 1952-1971; MS2014 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  The correspondence in this series are primarily original letters of thanks and/or praise, and a number of greeting cards. Some prominent correspondents include: John W. Hechinger, J. Willard Marriott, R.W. Van de Ville, and J.H. De Witt. These materials range in date from 1952 to 1971.
  - Hamilton, West Alexander, 1952 July 04 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Gardner, 1958 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - To Editor, 1958 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cox, Mrs. C. Rhodes, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Marsh, Mrs. Harold N., 1959 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Litschgi, Byrne, 1959 July 02 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Slayton, William L., 1959 July 02 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cook, Mabel R., 1959 July 06 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hechinger, John W., 1959 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jenkins Family, 1960 January 05 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Butler, Paul M., 1960 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ring, Jim, 1960 November 08 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Collins, M.S., 1960 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - De Witt, J.H., 1960 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lynch, Robert E., 1960 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - S. Kann and Sons Co., 1960 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hahn, Gilbert Jr., 1960 December 01 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Arthur Clarendon Sr., 1960 December 01 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Zamoiski, Joseph M., 1960 December 01 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hughes, William J. Jr., 1960 December 05 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Robinson, Robert, 1960 December 05 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Robinson, Robert, 1960 December 08 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rawlings, F.P. Jr., 1960 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Marriott, J. Willard, 1960 June 01 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Welling, A.C., 1960 July 05 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Waters, William H., 1970 April 01 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Van de Ville, R.W., 1971 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Van de Ville, R.W., 1971 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Arthur Clarendon Jr., n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - To President of the United States, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Speeches, statements, and remarks, 1961-1967; MS2014 Series 2; 1.25 Linear feet
  The materials in this series of speeches, statements and remarks are originals on paper and index cards. The material covers the years 1961-67. Many of these speeches, statements, and remarks were presented at schools and universities, public ceremonies, private celebrations, and board meetings. Some prominent subjects include: desegregation/integration in public schools, the Four Track Plan, city beautification and restoration, and the District of Columbia's 100th Year Anniversary.
  - Board of Education: Annual PTA Luncheon, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board of Education: Attainment Levels, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board of Education: Bolling v. Sharpe, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Board of Education: Borchardt, Selma M., n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board of Education: Citizens Role in Education, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Board of Education: Craftsmanship, 1959 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Board of Education: Current Affairs, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Board of Education: Desegregation, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Board of Education: Educational Equality, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Board of Education: Education System Overhaul, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Board of Education: Family Living Petition, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Board of Education: Four Track Plan, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Board of Education: Fraternities, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Board of Education: Graduation Ceremony, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Board of Education: Integration Problems/Historical Background, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Board of Education: Juvenile Delinquency Meeting, 1961 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Board of Education: Maintaining Standards, 1959 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Board of Education: Merritt School, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Board of Education: National Education Week, n.d., undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Ninth Annual Apprenticeship Convention, 1959 June 20 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Overholtzer, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Patterson, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Public Schooling, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Public Schooling/College Preparation, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Public Schooling/153rd Anniversary n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt High School Graduation Ceremony, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - School Board/Historical Background, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sharpe, Melvin.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sidwell Friends School -- 75th Anniversary, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vassar Club Luncheon, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board of Commissioners: Inaugural Speech, 1961 March 03 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board of Commissioners: Sutton, Chief Millard H., 1962 April 25 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Board of Commissioners: Princeton National Alumni Association Meeting, 1963 April 25 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board of Commissioners: Key to the City Ceremony -- General Clarke, 1963 July 08 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Board of Commissioners: Dedication of the Hyman Building/Washington Hospital Center, 1963 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Board of Commissioners: Kennedy Assassination, 1963 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Board of Commissioners: Christmas Address, 1963 December 22 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Board of Commissioners: Kingsbury, Marion -- Retirement, 1964 October 20 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Board of Commissioners: Safeway's International's Grand Opening, 1964 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Board of Commissioners: Key to the City Ceremony/Gian Carlo Menotti, 1965 January 22 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Board of Commissioners: Fyona, Edith A. -- Retirement, 1965 June 02 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Board of Commissioners: Morris Cafritz Memorial Swimming Pool, 1965 June 07 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Board of Commissioners: Kreeger, David, 1965 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Board of Commissioners: Martin, Bill -- Schinnerer, Victor, 1965 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Board of Commissioners: Dorothy Goldberg Day, 1965 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Board of Commissioners: Redskins, 1965 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Board of Commissioners: Presidential Crime Council Meeting, 1965 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Board of Commissioners: Vice President Humphrey's Meeting, 1966 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Board of Commissioners: Washington Metropolitan Police Department, 1966 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Board of Commissioners: District of Columbia's 100th Year Anniversary, 1966 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Board of Commissioners: Swearing in Ceremony -- Mathe, Brig. General Robert E., 1966 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Board of Commissioners: Elwood Davis Luncheon, 1966 December 29 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Board of Commissioners: F St. Plaza, 1967 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Board of Commissioners: Capital Hill Restoration Society, 1967 April 10 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Board of Commissioners: City Beautification Program, 1967 April 14 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Board of Commissioners: National Capitol Area Police/Community Relations Institute, 1967 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Board of Commissioners: Lowe, Schuyler -- Retirement, 1967 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Board of Commissioners: Reorganization for the District of Columbia, 1967 June 01 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Board of Commissioners: Reorganization Plan # 3, 1967 June 21 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Board of Commissioners: Government Operations, 1967 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Board of Commissioners: Summary of Actions Taken on Recommendations of D.C. Crime Commission Report, 1967 June 28 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Board of Commissioners: Statements of the Board of Commissioners, 1967 August 01 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Board of Commissioners: Washington, Walter E., 1967 September 20 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Board of Commissioners: Endorsement of D.C. Council Nominees, 1967 October 20 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Board of Commissioners: Altrusa Club, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Board of Commissioners: Brillat-Savarin-Escoffier, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Board of Commissioners: District Concerns, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Board of Commissioners: Duke -- Homage, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Board of Commissioners: Equal Employment Regulations, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Board of Commissioners: National Association of Broadcasters, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Board of Commissioners: National Retail Merchants Associations, n.d., undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Newspaper clippings, 1949-1964; MS2014 Series 3; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series consists of newspaper clippings. The personal news clippings are of family and friends, while the professional news clippings relate to Tobriner's time on the Board of Education. These professional news clippings cover subjects such as desegregation/integration in public schools, the Four Track Plan, school language programs, and teacher quality. The majority of these materials are undated, but many of them date from 1949 to 1964.
  - Personal: Bounds, Roger J., n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Personal: Ertz, Mrs. Coleridge, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Personal: Jewkes, John, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Personal: Marshall, Mrs. Walter, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Personal: Ray, James G., n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Personal: Sias, Don, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Personal: Stevens, A.B., n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Personal: Thomas, Lucretia, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Personal: Tobriner, Leon, 1953 November 03 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Personal: Tobriner, Marienne, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Personal: Tobriner, Matthew, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Personal: Tobriner, Matthew O., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Personal: Tobriner, Mrs. Leon, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Personal: Tobriner, Toby, 1949 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Personal: Wolf, Alfred/Connie, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Professional: Board of Education -- Miscellaneous, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Professional: City College, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Professional: Desegregation -- Integration, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Professional: Four Track Plan, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Professional: Hospital Council, 02/11/49, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Professional: Language Programs, 1960 December 25 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Professional: Neglect of Talent, 1958 November 04 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Professional: School Gains, 1958 November 04 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Professional: Superintendent of Schools, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Professional: Teacher Quality, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Professional: Tobriner's Appointment to the Board of Education, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Professional: Tobriner's Elected President of the Board of Education, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Professional: Tobriner Nomination for the D.C. Board of Commissioners, 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Professional: Tobriner's Reelected President os the Board of Education, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Publications, 1954-1960; MS2014 Series 4; 0.25 Linear feet
  The material consists of original and photocopied publications. The subjects of these publications vary, but most cover the topics of desegregation/integration in public schools and educational equality.
  - The Reporter, 1954 December 30 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - The Right of Every Child, April, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The Truth About Segregation in Washington's Schools, 1958 December 22 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Friends and Alumni Bulletin, June, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Stanford, 1960 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - The Scholastic Per6formance of Negro and White Pupils in the Integrated Public Schools of the District of Columbia, Summer, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bonanza, 1960 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, n.d., undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Scrapbooks, 1961-1968; MS2014 Series 5; 8 Linear feet
  This series contains scrapbooks with newspaper clippings, photographs, invitations, correspondence, publications, speeches and various sorts of memorabilia. These materials range in date from 1961 to 1968 and are arranged according to the original order of the scrapbooks. The scrapbooks are in chronological order of about one year intervals, with the exception of boxes 11 through 13 which date from 1964 to 1968.
  This series consists mainly of records corresponding to the time that Tobriner served on the Board of Education and the Board of Commissioners for the Washington D.C. Area, but also refers to his work as chairman of the Washington Metro Area Transit Authority and time spent as the United States Ambassador to Jamaica. The materials in this series cover a number of topics with much consideration: civil rights issues, welfare reforms, school reforms, fire and police force modifications, freeway and subway plans, city beautification, crime, voting rights, and the D.C. Government Plan. Additionally, there is a substantial amount of memorabilia relating to the President of the United States, Washington Area civic and social functions. civil rights protests, and Tobriner's time in Jamaica.
  - Page 1, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Page 2, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Page 3, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Page 4, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Page 5, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Page 6, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Page 7, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Page 8, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Page 9, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Page 10, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Page 11, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Page 12, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Page 13, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Page 14, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Page 15, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Page 16, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Page 17, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Page 18, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Page 19, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Page 20, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Page 21, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Page 22, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Page 23, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Page 24, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Page 25, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Page 26, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Page 27, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Page 28, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Page 29, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Page 30, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Page 31, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Page 32, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Page 33, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Page 34, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Page 35, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Page 36, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Page 37, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Page 38, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Page 39, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Page 40, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Page 41, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Page 42, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Page 43, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Page 44, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Page 45, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Page 46, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Page 47, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Page 48, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Page 49, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Page 50, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Page 51, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Page 52, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Page 53, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Page 54, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Page 55, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Page 56, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Page 57, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Page 58, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Page 59, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Page 60, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Page 61, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Page 62, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Page 63, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Page 64, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Page 65, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Page 66, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Page 67, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Page 68, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Page 69, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Page 70, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Page 71, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Page 72, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Page 73, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Page 74, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Page 75, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Page 76, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Page 77, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Page 78, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Page 79, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Page 80, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Page 81, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Page 82, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Page 83, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Page 84, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Page 85, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Page 86, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Page 87, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Page 88, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Page 89, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Page 90, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Page 91, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Page 92, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Page 93, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Page 94, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Page 95, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Page 96, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Page 97, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Page 98, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Page 99, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Page 100, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Page 101, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Page 102, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Page 103, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Page 104, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Page 105, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Page 106, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Page 107, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Page 108, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Page 109, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Page 110, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Page 111, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Page 112, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Page 113, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Page 114, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Page 115, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Page 116, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 36)